**2X Meal Match:** Turn $1 into $2. Help serve more meals to young people. [**Give Today.**](https://www.covenanthouse.org/thanksgiving-meal-match?sourceid=2503935&origin=DHQEI2505DLABN)

Close Alert

 Search

 Search

* Youth Homelessness

    Know the Issues

    Who It Affects

* Our Work

    The Youth Journey

    Our Impact

* Get Involved

    Ways to Give

    Take Action

* About Us

* Youth Homelessness
    
    4.2 million youth experience homelessness each year

    Know the Issues

    Who It Affects

* Our Work
    
    From Crisis to Care: A Journey of Youth Homelessness
    
    What happens when a young person enters our doors? We welcome them with open arms.

    The Youth Journey

    Our Impact

* Get Involved
    
    Join the Movement to End Youth Homelessness
    
    There are many ways to take action in support of youth facing homelessness.

    Ways to Give

    Take Action

* About Us
    
    We Provide Love, Shelter and Hope to Young People Facing Homelessness
    
    Since 1972, Covenant House has opened its doors to over 1.5 million young people experiencing homelessness and trafficking, one youth at a time. 

Covenant House Privacy Policy
=============================

Security
--------

Covenant House understands the importance of protecting your personal information. Giving a tax-deductible donation to Covenant House is safe and credit card information is protected by a reputable security company, and numbers are never stored.

On our donation pages, please make note of the domain name in your website address bar. The name there begins with "https," which indicates that the page is encrypted. Encryption actually makes your online donation more secure than using a credit card in physical form at a store, restaurant, or any other place of business.

If you have any questions regarding the security of online donations, please [contact us](mailto:info@covenanthouse.org).

Domain Name
-----------

Our web server automatically recognizes but does not collect or use your domain name (IP address). We anonymously track your visit in order to compile statistical information about the use of our site. We do not collect information about you or your personal use of this site.

Covenant House uses cookies, which are small amounts of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your hard drive to see if you are a returning user or to allow our online community to recognize you as an existing member. We do not use cookies to collect any personal information from your computer.

Email Addresses
---------------

If you would like to opt out of email communications at any time, just click the Unsubscribe link included at the bottom of every Covenant House email communication. You may also [contact us](mailto:info@covenanthouse.org) at any time to be removed from our distribution list.

Other Personal Information
--------------------------

You are not required to provide any personal information on our website unless you choose to do so. However, in order to properly process charitable gifts, we do ask for personal information on our online donation pages. We use this information to acknowledge receipt of your donation for tax purposes.

When you donate to Covenant House, you are placed on mailing lists for mail and email updates. If you do not wish to receive physical mail from Covenant House, please [contact us](mailto:info@covenanthouse.org). If you are making a donation in honor or memory of someone, we will not use his or her personal information for any purpose other than to send an acknowledgment card.

We may occasionally make postal addresses and email addresses available to other reputable nonprofit and commercial organizations. If you do not want us to share this information, please [contact us](mailto:info@covenanthouse.org).

Opt-Out
-------

If at any time you wish to stop receiving emails from Covenant House, simply follow the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email or contact Covenant House at [news@CovenantHouse.org](mailto:news@CovenantHouse.org).

Our website has links to others whose privacy policies may differ from ours. Covenant House is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of these other sites.

Our donors' goodwill and generosity are very important to us – and so is your privacy. If you feel that your privacy has been violated or that Covenant House has misused your information in any way, please [contact us](mailto:info@covenanthouse.org).

Data Collected When You Sign Up for Our Texts
---------------------------------------------

Text messaging originator opt-in data and consent will not be shared with any third party.

Terms and Conditions
--------------------

By opting into Covenant House’s text messaging list you agree to these terms:

Covenant House will send you five text messages per month on average. For help, text HELP to REFUGE or email [info@covenanthouse.org](mailto:info@covenanthouse.org). Text STOP to REFUGE to opt out of text messages. Message and data rates may apply. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.

Stay Informed

Join our email newsletter to learn more about how we’re working to end youth homelessness.

 Submit

Covenant House is a nonprofit 501(c)(3) organization; EIN/Tax ID number: [13-2725416](https://www.covenanthouse.org/about-us/financials) | DUNS number: 07-520-9411

© 2024 Covenant House International. All rights reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://www.covenanthouse.org/privacy-policy)

Close
